ILGWU. Irwin Solomon papers, 5780/187
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. Irwin Solomon papers
1965-1998.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union;
Solomon, Irwin.
5780/187
47.5 cubic feet
47.5 linear feet
Records
Contains the files of Irwin Solomon during his tenure as Executive Vice President and later General Secretary-Treasurer of the ILGWU. The collection consists primarily of correspondence files, but also includes financial reports and files pertaining to the merger of the ILGWU and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers of America to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE).
6323209
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
June 2011
EAD encoding:
Cheryl Beredo, June 2011
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was founded in New York City in 1900 by mostly Socialist immigrant workers who sought to unite the various crafts in the growing women's garment industry. The union soon reflected changes in the sector and rapidly organized thousands of unskilled and semi-skilled women, mostly Jewish and Italian young immigrants. Exemplifying the "new unionism," the ILGWU led two of the most widespread and best-known industrial strikes of the early Twentieth Century: the shirtwaist makers' strike of 1909 in New York City and the cloak makers' strike of 1910 in Chicago. The union also tried to adapt to the fragmented and unstable nature of the industry. It adopted the "protocol of peace," a system of industrial relations that attempted to ensure stability and limit strikes and production disruption by providing for an arbitration system to resolve disputes.
The ILGWU exemplified the European-style social unionism of its founding members. They pursued bread and butter issues but provided educational opportunities, benefits, and social programs to union members as well. In 1919, the ILGWU became the first American union to negotiate an unemployment compensation fund that was contributed to by its employers. The ILGWU also pioneered in the establishment of an extremely progressive health care program for its members which included not only regional Union Health Centers but also a resort for union workers, known as Unity House. The Union also had an imaginative and pioneering Education Department which not only trained workers in traditional union techniques, but provided courses in citizenship and the English language.
David Dubinsky, an immigrant from Belarus who came to the US in 1911, provided strong leadership that led to unprecedented growth in the union during his presidency from 1932 to 1966. He led the union through successful internal anti-communist struggles, built on the ascendancy of industrial unionism by encouraging the formation of the Committee for Industrial Organization, and helped the union become an important political force in New York City and state politics, and in the national Democratic Party and Liberal Party as well.
In the period following the Second World War, the union suffered a decline in membership as manufacturers avoided unionization and took advantage of less expensive labor by moving shops from the urban centers in the northeast to the south, and later abroad. The ethnic and racial character of the ILGWU also changed as European immigrants were supplanted by Asians, Latin Americans, African- Americans, and immigrants from the Caribbean.
In July 1995 the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) at a joint convention, forming UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees). At the time the new union had a membership of about 250,000 in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Biographical / Historical
Irwin Solomon was born April 22nd, 1926, in Crown Heights, Brooklyn. In 1947, Solomon became auditor of the ILGWU. For a period, he worked as financial secretary of the Philadelphia Joint Board, then as manager of Local 190 in Philadelphia, and then as manager of the Philadelphia Joint Board. From 1983 to 1986, Solomon was Executive Vice President of the ILGWU. From 1986 until his retirement in 1995, Solomon served as Secretary-Treasurer of the ILGWU. Before retiring, he was involved in negotiating the 1995 merger of the ILGWU with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union to create Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE).
Scope and Contents
Contains the files of Irwin Solomon during his tenure as Executive Vice President and later General Secretary-Treasurer of the ILGWU. The collection consists primarily of correspondence files, but also includes financial reports and files pertaining to the merger of the ILGWU and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers of America to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE).
Conditions Governing Access
The ILGWU Records, except for publications and materials produced for publication, are restricted. Materials created prior to twenty years from the current date are open to researchers only with prior written permission from the Director of the Kheel Center; materials created during the past twenty-years are closed; the minutes of the General Executive Board are closed. For more information contact the Kheel Center.
Related Materials
5780. ILGWU records
General
"Permanent deposit"
Women's clothing industry--New York (State)--New York; Women's clothing industry--United States.; Labor unions--Clothing workers--New York (State)--New York; Labor unions--Clothing workers--United States.; Clothing workers--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers--United States.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; Solomon, Irwin; Solomon, Irwin, b. 1926; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.
6323209
- National Retirement Fund, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- New Jersey Region, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Recession, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ORT Federation, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Department for Professional Employees Reports, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Jay Mazur [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Jay Mazur [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Western Asset Management, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Donald Fischer, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Susan Cowell, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Perry Parker, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Central States Region, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Buck Pension Fund Incorporated, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Bear Stearns Asset Management, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Chase Manhattan Bank, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Stratford Advisory Group, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- T. Rowe Price Associates, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- ILGWU General Fund: Policies and Objectives (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Arnold and Porter, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Canadian Office, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Allentown Collection Control [folder 1 of 2], 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Allentown Collection Control [folder 2 of 2], 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Russell Clough, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Chaikin and Chaikin, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Contract Labor Bills, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Computers [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Computers [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Fund Raising [folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Fund Raising [folder 2 of 2], 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meeting Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meeting Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meeting Reports, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Union Health Center, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Hertz, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Imports [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Imports [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Histadrut, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Knitted Outerwear Manufacturers Association, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Invitations, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Insurance, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Investment Committee: General Funds, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Investment Summary: T. Rowe Price, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  July - December
- Leader Data Processing [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Leader Data Processing [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- American ORT Federation, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Organization, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Northeast Region, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Northeast Apparel Association, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Non-Assessable, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Albert Nipon, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Midwest Region, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- New York State District, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- New York Joint Board, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- New York Joint Board Health and Welfare Module, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- New York Coat, Suit, and Dress, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- New Jersey Region, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Liquidated Damages, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Local 10, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Local 23-25, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Local 62-32, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Local 62-40, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Local 91, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Local 99, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Local 102, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Local 153, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Local 155, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Proposal for Staff Health Plan, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Investment Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Perry Parker, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- James Parrott, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Collection Control, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  August
- Irwin Solomon [folder 1 of 3], 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 2 of 3], 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 3 of 3], 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico District Council, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico: Barranquitas, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rico, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Retiree Services, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Staff Retirement, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- TPF and C [folder 1 of 2], 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- TPF and C [folder 2 of 2], 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Union Health Center, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Union Label, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Union Health Center: Jay Mazur, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Sol Berger, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Jay Mazur, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Jay Mazur [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Jay Mazur [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Jay Mazur [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Jay Mazur [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Jay Mazur, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Susan Cowell, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Donald Fischer [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Donald Fischer [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 1 of 3], 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 2 of 3], 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 3 of 3], 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  June 30
- General Fund, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  December 31
- Death Benefit Fund, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  September 30
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Death Benefit Fund, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  March 31
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- General Fund, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- General Fund, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- National Retirement Fund, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- General Fund, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- National Retirement Fund, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- General Fund, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- General Fund, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- General Fund, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank [folder 1 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank [folder 2 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Benefits, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Campaign Committee, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Chaikin and Chaikin, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Deborah Hospital Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Education, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Fashion Institute Technology (FIT), 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Fashion Institute Technology (FIT): Degree Programs, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board (GEB), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- General Fund, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meeting: Baltimore, MD, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  October 11- 13
- Midwest Region, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- New England Region, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- New England Region: Leon Roth (Box 15, Folder 2)
- New Jersey Region, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Newmark, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Northeast Department, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Organizing Department, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Pacific Northwest, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Personal, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Department for Professional Employees, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Personal: Solomon, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  contains 11 photo duplicates of an Irwin Solomon portrait
- Philadelphia, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT): Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  April 18
- Midwest Region, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Local 155, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Histadrut, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Hilton Hotel, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Leader Data Processing, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Legal, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board (GEB) WED, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  May 31
- Bear Stearns Asset Management, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Fidelity Investments, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Glickenhaus and Company, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Lehman Ark Management, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Neuberg and Berman, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- T. Rowe Price, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Local 91, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Local 102, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Political, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rico, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Retiree Service Department, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Roundabout, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Roundabout Construction Charges, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Roundabout Leases, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Ship'n Shore [folder 1 of 2], 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Ship'n Shore [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Solidarity Day, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Southeast Region, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- South Jersey, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Staff Retirement, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Stratford Advisory, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Subpoena, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Taskforce [folder 1 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Taskforce [folder 2 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Task Force: Finance, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Individual Profit, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- General Finance, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Unity House [folder 1 of 2], 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Unity House [folder 2 of 2], 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  contains 11 photos
- South Jersey Joint Board: U.S. Department of Labor, 1977-1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Welfare Fund Control [folder 1 of 2], 1983-1986 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Welfare Fund Control [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Solomon: Personal, 1981-1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Western States, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Western States: Building Information [folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Western States: Building Information [folder 2 of 2], 1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Union Health Center, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Union Sanatorium, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Unity House [folder 1 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Unity House [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Financial, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Correspondence and Reports, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Correspondence and Reports [folder 1 of 4], 1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Correspondence and Reports [folder 2 of 4], 1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Correspondence and Reports [folder 3 of 4], 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Correspondence and Reports [folder 4 of 4], 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- UNITE Administrative Income and Costs, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Irwin Solomon: Signed Releases, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- K-Mart, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank Correspondence, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  November
- UNITE Technology Plan by Ernst and Young, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- UNITE Online Data Network Report (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Senior Citizens News, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  June - July
- UNITE Bargaining Unit Directory, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  June
- General Executive Board Meetings, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- A. H. Schreiber, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Analysis of Personnel Reductions, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- UNITE General Fund Statements, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- UNITE Strike and Defense Statements, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- UNITE Schedule of Administrative Expenses, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- UNITE Schedule of Organizational Areas Expenses, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Reserve Funds Statement, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Correspondence and Reports, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- UNITE Staff Retirement Plan, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  December 22
- UNITE/153 Agreement, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  September 28
- UNITE Employees Report, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  January 15
- UNITE Product Directory, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Arnold and Porter, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Wolf and Schulman, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Real Property Tax Analysis (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Newmark Real Estate: Lease Information (Box 24, Folder 7)
- General Fund Financial Statements, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  September
- EPR-ILGWU Financial Statements, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  July - August
- Realty Holding Corporation Financial Statements, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  December 1995 - October 1996
- Local 91 Realty Corporation Financial Statements, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Joint Board Dress Building Incorporated Financial Statements, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  December 1995 - January 1996
- 1710 Broadway Incorporated Financial Statements, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  December 1995 - December 1996
- Amalgamated Bank: Irwin and Sylvia Solomon, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  December 1995 - September 1997
- Amalgamated Bank: ILGWU General Fund, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank: ILGWU General Fund, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Bank: ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Neuberger and Berman: UNITE Portfolio Review, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- W. P. Capital Management: UNITE Portfolio Review, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Koch Asset Management: UNITE Portfolio Review, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Glickenhaus and Company: UNITE Death Benefit Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Shroders: ILGWU Health Services Plan, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  September 1995 - December 1996
- Pacific Investment Management Group: ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- J. P. Morgan: ILGWU General Fund, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  December
- J. P. Morgan: ILGWU General Fund, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- J. P. Morgan: ILGWU General Fund, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Goldman Sachs: ILGWU Fixed Income Portfolio, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  September 1995 - August 1996
- Goldman Sachs: ILGWU Fixed Income Portfolio, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  September 1996 - January 1997
- Brandywine Asset Management: UNITE, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Towers Perrin: Asset Management (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Towers Perrin: UNITE General Fund Third Quarter, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Towers Perrin: UNITE General Fund Fourth Quarter, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Towers Perrin: UNITE General Fund First Quarter, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Towers Perrin: UNITE General Fund Second Quarter [folder 1 of 2], 1996 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  3 copies total
- Towers Perrin: UNITE General Fund Second Quarter [folder 2 of 2], 1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Towers Perrin: UNITE General Fund Third Quarter, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  2 copies
- Towers Perrin: Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund First Quarter, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Towers Perrin: Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund Second Quarter, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Towers Perrin: Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund Third Quarter, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Towers Perrin: Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund Fourth Quarter, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Towers Perrin: ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  August 2
- Towers Perrin: ILGWU National Retirement Fund Third Quarter, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Towers Perrin: UNITE Staff Retirement Fund Third Quarter, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Towers Perrin: UNITE Staff Retirement Fund Fourth Quarter, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Towers Perrin: Death Benefit Fund Third Quarter, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Towers Perrin: Death Benefit Fund Third Quarter, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Towers Perrin: Death Benefit Fund Fourth Quarter, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Eastern Pennsylvania Region Publication, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- UNITE Publication, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  English, French, Spanish, Chinese
- Charges: John Newman, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Retirement Plan Information, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- General Execute Board (GEB) Meeting, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  January 6-12
- Personnel, 1985-1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Mergers, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Personnel Review (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Frank Rossi, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Joint Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Unaffiliated Locals List, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Arnold Harris: Meeting, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Lease Information, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- UNITE Tax Exemption, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Malden Mills, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- UNITE Education Department Staff, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- General, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- General Execute Board (GEB): Report, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Buildings, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Puerto Rico, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- James Parrott, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Saul Rosen, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Staff Retirement, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Member Assistance Program, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Task Force on Associate Membership Report, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  October 16
- Task Force: Social Services, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Task Force: General Executive Board (GEB), 1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Union Health Center [folder 1 of 3], 1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Union Health Center [folder 2 of 3], 1987 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Union Health Center [folder 3 of 3], 1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Research Department, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Retiree Services, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Secretaries and Treasurers, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Paul Segal Associates Architects, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Department for Professional Employees, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Professional and Clerical Employees (PACE), 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Pacific Northwest, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Organizing Department, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- ORT, 1986-1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Hermine Hart, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 8)